colorlines.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy | Colorlines

#### Race Forward and Colorlines Privacy Statement

This Web site is operated and maintained by [Race Forward](https://www.raceforward.org/), a national organization advancing racial justice though research, media and practice.

Race Forward is committed to protecting your privacy and providing a rewarding online experience. This Privacy Policy describes Race Forward’s policies and procedures for the collection of personal information by this site, and our use and dissemination of such information.

#### Information Gathering

If you subscribe to, purchase or otherwise make use of our products and services, we may ask to collect personal information from you, including your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit card number (only when making purchases) and facts about your computers, profession and similar information.

Cookies: We use “cookies” to help deliver advertisements and to identify unique browsers that visit us and to track usage throughout our sites.

#### Information Use and Sharing

In order to better serve our readers, we use cookies and periodically analyze web logs. We may also use third-party services such as Google Analytics (including Google Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting). This helps us understand traffic patterns and know if there are problems with our website. For more information about how Google collects and uses this information, please see [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can opt out of Google’s Analytics Demographic and Interest Reporting by changing the [ad settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) associated with your Google account.

If you choose to subscribe to Colorlines Direct, our free weekly electronic newsletter, we collect your email address, and, if you choose to provide it, additional information such as your zip code. Race Forward will never sell or share your information. We reserve the right to send out emails for events and new releases on behalf of partner organizations but we never share your information.

#### Links

Our sites may contain links to other sites, in the form of hyperlinks and banner advertisements. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our sites, or your dealings with our sites, please contact websters@raceforward.org.
